Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Drama, Honors Theses SC4-4596
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Department of Drama, honors theses
1991-2009
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. Department of Drama
SC4-4596
1 Linear Feet (11 volumes in 3 boxes)
Honors theses written by undergraduate students in the Stanford University Department of Drama.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the Stanford University Archives by the Department of Drama in 2005. Additional theses were transferred to the Stanford University Archives from the Hume Writing Center in 2011.
Scope and Contents note
This collection consists of honors theses written by undergraduate students in the Stanford University Department of Drama.
Access to Collection
The collection is open for research use; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use. No photocopies may be made.
Drama; Student papers.; Stanford University. Department of Drama
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2005-030
  - Cohen, Megan, Never Enough: Qualities of Time in the Work of Forced Entertainment., May 23, 2005 (Box 1)
  - Griffin, Matthew Hunter, Beyond repair; reading Goat Island through the lens of Walter Benjamin., 2004 (Box 1)
  - Jackson, Daniel, Drunk, Naked, Out of Control: Radiohole saves the American theatrical avant-garde., May 18, 2005 (Box 1)
  - Kaltman, Jessica, Bureaucracy, censorship, and controversy: a comparative analysis of the Federal Theatre Project and National Endowment for the Arts., 2004 (Box 1)
  - Larson, Brian, Holy Desire: Sebastian's sexual restlessness and his break out of the closet in Tennessee Williams' Suddenly Last Summer., 2004 (Box 1)
  - Vargas, Lisa, From real to reel: imitations between news and film., 2004 (Box 1)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2011-152
  - Hilfinger-Pardo, Paz, "What did one architect say to the other architect?": exposing the structure of narrative in Architecting and The Sound and the Fury (April Seventh, 1928)., 2009 (Box 1)
  - Goddard, Leslie, Brontë: creating a one-woman show., 1991 (Box 1)
  - Cunha, Anne Lewis, The extraordinary and subversive power of the dramatic dream, from Shakespeare to the contemporary theater: a study of the dream as a dramatic device., 1998 (Box 1)
  - Gadda, Jennifer, CASM: computer-aided stage manager., 2000 (Box 1)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2018-060
  - Fried, Steven, "Habeas corpus: Meyerhold, the final chapter", 2002 (Box 1)